So now that we've done the first two steps of our phone call situation where we're going to invite a
所以现在我们已经完成了电话情况的前两个步骤，我们将邀请一个
friend we can actually get to the phrases that we can use to invite.
朋友，我们实际上可以找到我们可以用来邀请的短语。
Now I want to avoid using very fake sounding phrases like I would like to invite you to go out to dinner
现在我想避免使用听起来很假的短语，比如我想请你出去吃饭
with me.
与我一起。
Don't don't do that unless you're talking to the Queen of England.
除非你在和英国女王交谈，否则不要这样做。
Nobody actually speaks that way.
实际上没有人会那样说话。
It's way too formal.
太正式了
So we need to look at some informal ways to do an invitation.
所以我们需要看看一些非正式的邀请方式。
Informal invitations.
非正式邀请。
OK so how can we do it naturally.
好的，那么我们如何自然地做到这一点。
Remember we're inviting someone to go and eat something with us.
请记住，我们正在邀请某人和我们一起吃点东西。
So let's do this.
所以让我们这样做。
Let's let's.
让我们吧。
Let's look at a couple of phrases.
让我们看几个短语。
I was thinking this is very common.
我在想这很常见。
I was thinking I was thinking now this is a very common phrase to use in invitations because it makes
我在想我现在在想这是在邀请中使用的一个非常常见的短语，因为它使
it feel like there's not too much pressure on you.
感觉对你没有太大的压力。
It feels like I'm planning to do this.
感觉就像我打算这样做。
And if you decide not to go it's no big deal.
如果你决定不去，那也没什么大不了的。
I don't want to put too much pressure on you.
我不想给你太大压力。
If I say please please have lunch with me.
如果我说请和我一起吃午饭。
We know what's wrong with you.
我们知道你怎么了。
It's a little too.
这也有点。
Too much pressure.
太大压力。
So we want to we want to be kind of relaxed and this is the right.
所以我们想要我们想要放松，这是正确的。
This is the right phrase.
这是正确的短语。
I was thinking of going to grab a bite to eat to grab.
我正想着去抢点吃的去抢。
Which is a very common word in English used which actually means this grab.
这是英语中非常常用的一个词，实际上意味着这种抓取。
But actually it can often mean get it can often mean get and it can often mean by grab a bite.
但实际上它通常意味着得到它通常意味着得到它通常意味着咬一口。
This is a common phrase a bite to eat I eat.
这是一句常用的一句话，一口吃，一口吃。
OK.
好的。
I was thinking of going to grab a bite to eat going to grab a sandwich going to grab a cup of coffee
我在想去吃点东西去吃三明治去喝咖啡
going to grab a hamburger.
要去拿一个汉堡。
Doesn't mean you're going to grab it and run.
并不意味着你会抓住它然后跑。
It just means you're going to get that.
这只是意味着你会得到它。
It's a it's a very relaxed and casual way to say it.
这是一种非常轻松和随意的说法。
OK.
好的。
That's a common phrase probably I don't know if it's number one but up there with one of the most common
这是一个常见的短语，我可能不知道它是否是第一名，但它是最常见的短语之一
or maybe it's a group.
或者，也许它是一个群体。
Me and some friends.
我和一些朋友。
This is another way to say this is happening.
这是说这种情况正在发生的另一种方式。
So if you decide not to go it's not a big deal in American culture.
所以如果你决定不去，这在美国文化中没什么大不了的。
It's important not to pressure people too much if you say I really really really need you to be there.
如果你说我真的真的真的需要你在场，不要给别人太多压力，这一点很重要。
That will only be in a few situations.
这只会在少数情况下发生。
It's pretty rare.
这是相当罕见的。
Generally we want to give people the feeling of freedom if you decide not to go it's OK.
一般来说，如果你决定不去没关系，我们想给人们自由的感觉。
I'd like you to be there but it's OK if you don't if you don't go.
我希望你在那里，但如果你不去也没关系。
Me and some friends maybe you've learned some friends and I.
我和一些朋友也许你和我认识了一些朋友。
But we can also say me and some friends.
但我们也可以说我和一些朋友。
Many people use it.
许多人使用它。
Are are going out tonight.
今晚要出去。
Now usually going out this phrase going out that's an OH YOU'LL GET USED TO MY HANDWRITING going out
现在通常出去这个短语出去那是一个哦你会习惯我的手写出去
tonight.
今晚。
That means having drinks probably maybe going to a bar or a nightclub.
这意味着喝酒可能会去酒吧或夜总会。
It generally means you're going to have a beer or alcohol or what we call drinks.
这通常意味着您要喝啤酒或酒精或我们所说的饮料。
If somebody says Would you like to get a drink.
如果有人说你想喝一杯吗？
It doesn't mean let's go have some milk.
这并不意味着我们去喝点牛奶。
It would be funny.
这会很有趣。
It means let's get some alcohol.
这意味着让我们喝点酒。
So me and some friends are going out tonight.
所以我和一些朋友今晚要出去。
Would you Would you.
你愿意吗。
Now this is this is very polite but still natural.
现在这是非常礼貌的，但仍然很自然。
Would you care care or like to come along.
你会在乎还是愿意一起来。
Do you care to come along.
你愿意一起来。
Would you like to come along.
你要一起来吗。
Do you want to come along is also OK.
你想一起来也行。
Do you want to come along.
你要不要一起来。
Would you like to come along.
你要一起来吗。
Would you care to come along.
你愿意一起来吗？
Very common all of them.
都很常见。
Again this is a way to invite someone to do something that you're already going to do anyway.
同样，这是一种邀请某人做你已经要做的事情的方式。
OK.
好的。
Let's look at some other phrases.
让我们看看其他一些短语。
I'm starving.
我饿死了。
That means dying from hunger.
这意味着死于饥饿。
Often when we speak in English we we exaggerate a little we say a little bit more than we actually mean.
通常，当我们说英语时，我们夸大了一点，说的比实际意思多一点。
So if someone says I'm starving are they actually starving.
所以如果有人说我饿了，他们真的饿了。
Are they actually dying from hunger.
他们真的饿死了吗？
New new.
新新。
But we say it as a way to make what we are saying a little bit stronger.
但我们这样说是为了让我们所说的更有说服力。
It's a common way to do it.
这是一种常见的方法。
If somebody says I'm dying or oh it's killing me my head is killing me.
如果有人说我快死了，或者说我快要死了，我的头快要死了。
They're not actually dying their head is not actually killing them.
他们实际上并没有死，他们的头并没有真正杀死他们。
It's a way to express something is very strong it's very painful it's killing me.
这是一种表达某事的方式，它非常强烈，非常痛苦，这让我感到很痛苦。
I'm so hungry I'm starving.
我太饿了，快饿死了。
It's common very common.
很常见很常见。
I'm starving.
我饿死了。
Want to want to go get something to eat.
想去想去吃点东西。
Want to go get something to eat and instead of saying want to go get something to eat.
想去吃点东西，而不是说想去吃点东西。
We often use to or to make it sound more natural more smooth want to go get something to eat and instead
我们经常使用 to or to make it sound more natural 更流畅 想去吃点东西，而不是
of saying want to we might say one to one to want to is the same as saying one when we're speaking naturally
说想要我们可能会一对一地说想要与我们自然说话时说一个是一样的
we'll often say one to one to go get.
我们会经常一对一说去搞定。
Now you might have heard that go and get shouldn't be together but actually in some cases it's common.
现在你可能听说 go 和 get 不应该在一起，但实际上在某些情况下它很常见。
We're gonna go there and then we're going to get it.
我们要去那里，然后我们会得到它。
We could say Go get we could say go grab you want to go grab something to eat you want to go grab a
我们可以说去拿 我们可以说去抢 你想去抢东西吃 你想去抢
coffee you want to go grab a sandwich or a burger.
咖啡你想去拿三明治或汉堡。
Very common.
很常见。
Want to go get something to eat.
想去吃点东西。
I'm starving.
我饿死了。
Let's go get something to eat.
我们去吃点东西吧。
Want to go get something to eat.
想去吃点东西。
OK.
好的。
All very common.
都很常见。
Now I want to just mentioned one thing we can't say want to join me after this.
现在我只想提一件事，我们不能说想在此之后加入我。
I'm starving.
我饿死了。
Want to join me because you didn't say what thing you're going to do in the first so when we said I'm
想加入我，因为你一开始没有说你要做什么，所以当我们说我是
going to go grab something I'm going to go grab lunch I'm going to go grab something to eat.
我要去拿东西我要去吃午饭我要去拿东西吃。
Want to join me.
想加入我。
Want to join me or want to join me because I said what I'm going to do then I can say Join me.
想加入我或想加入我，因为我说了我要做什么然后我可以说加入我。
But if I say I'm starving then it doesn't make sense to say do you want to come along.
但如果我说我快饿死了，那么说你要不要一起来是没有意义的。
Do you want to join me because I didn't say what I'm doing.
你想加入我吗，因为我没有说我在做什么。
I just said how I feel.
我只是说我的感受。
So now I should say want to go get something to eat.
所以现在我应该说想去吃点东西。
Now I have to make the request first I say what I feel and then I ask you if you want to do what I would
现在我必须先提出请求 我说我的感受 然后我问你是否愿意做我想做
like to do with me.
喜欢和我做。
Now here's another one that's really common when we want to make somebody feel that they can say yes
现在，当我们想让某人觉得他们可以说是时，这是另一个非常常见的方法
or no.
或者没有。
And it's OK because I'm going to do it anyway.
没关系，因为无论如何我都会这样做。
So if I say I'm about to.
所以如果我是的，我即将。
If somebody says I'm about to that means it's going to happen very soon.
如果有人说我即将这样做，那意味着它很快就会发生。
This is a way of saying something will be soon you wouldn't say about two if it's maybe in a year.
这是一种说某事很快就会发生的方式，如果可能在一年内，您不会说两个。
I'm about to get a job.
我要找工作了。
That doesn't mean in a year that means maybe this week it's very soon OK.
这并不意味着在一年内这意味着也许本周它很快就会好起来的。
I'm about to I'm about to have dinner and we could.
我要吃晚饭了，我们可以。
Of course we could also say we could add go if you want to say go have dinner.
当然，如果你想说去吃饭，我们也可以说我们可以加去。
About to have dinner.
正要吃晚饭。
I'm about to go have dinner fun.
我要去吃晚饭了。
I'm about to have dinner then.
那我就要吃晚饭了。
Hungry Hungry.
饿了饿了。
It means are you hungry but often native English speakers instead of saying are you will cancel are
这意味着你饿了，但通常以英语为母语的人而不是说你会取消是
you.
你。
Or is it in many situations and just say one word.
还是在很多情况下只说一句话。
But you have to say it with the right tone.
但是你必须用正确的语气说出来。
For example we might say are you ready.
例如，我们可能会说你准备好了吗？
Now notice my voice goes Dent dent into Dent and then the.
现在注意我的声音从 Dent 到 Dent，然后是。
Are you ready.
你准备好了吗。
But often we'll just cancel are you.
但通常我们只会取消你。
Instead we'll say ready.
相反，我们会说准备好了。
Ready.
准备好。
But if you say ready that means I am ready because of the tone.
但如果你说准备好了，那意味着我已经准备好了，因为语气。
Are you ready.
你准备好了吗。
I am ready.
我准备好了。
Ready.
准备好。
But for hungry we don't usually say hungry.
但是对于饿了，我们通常不会说饿了。
Sounds a little weird.
听起来有点奇怪。
Hungry.
饥饿的。
Yes.
是的。
Is the right answer.
是正确答案。
Starving.
挨饿。
Not so much.
没那么多。
Hungry.
饥饿的。
Yes.
是的。
It's very common.
这很常见。
Hungry.
饥饿的。
Yes.
是的。
Now this means.
现在这意味着。
Do you want to eat with me even though I didn't exactly say do you want to eat with me.
你想和我一起吃饭吗，即使我没有说你想和我一起吃饭。
It's suggested by me being here asking you if I just say hungry and you say yes.
建议我在这里问你我是否只是说饿了，你说是的。
Then I said OK let's go right now and you sound.
然后我说好的，我们现在就走，你的声音。
No no no no no no no.
不不不不不不不。
I don't want to eat with you.
我不想和你一起吃饭。
I'm hungry.
我饿了。
I have my food right here.
我的食物就在这里。
That would be so so rude and very very bad.
那将是如此粗鲁，非常非常糟糕。
If you say yes to hungry what you're really saying yes to is going with me to eat.
如果你对饥饿说“是”，那么你真正说“是”就是和我一起去吃饭。
If I say I'm starving I'm about to go have dinner.
如果我说我饿了，我就要去吃晚饭了。
Hungry.
饥饿的。
And you say yeah it means yes.
你说是的，这意味着是的。
And I would like to go eat with you.
我想和你一起去吃饭。
It doesn't mean yes I'm hungry but I'm going to eat by myself.
这并不意味着我饿了，但我要自己吃饭。
No no no.
不不不。
Saying you're hungry is although you're not saying it directly is saying yes to going with me.
说你饿了，虽然你没有直接说，但就是同意和我一起去。
So that's important to keep in mind.
所以记住这一点很重要。
Sometimes when we say something what we really mean is underneath.
有时，当我们说某事时，我们真正的意思是在下面。
Right.
正确的。
It's suggested based on the situation based on what's happening care for a cup of coffee.
建议根据情况根据发生的情况照顾一杯咖啡。
Care for what does that mean here.
关心这里是什么意思。
Well actually we're not saying it but really there is a would you would you care for is the same as
好吧实际上我们并没有说它，但真的有一个你会关心的事情是一样的
saying Would you like if I have some chocolate here and I say Would you like a piece of chocolate then
说如果我在这里有一些巧克力你要不要我说那你要一块巧克力吗
you can say Oh yes please I would like a piece of chocolate.
你可以说哦，是的，我想要一块巧克力。
That's a common thing to say but I could just say care for a piece of chocolate.
这是一个常见的说法，但我只能说关心一块巧克力。
Care for a piece of chocolate and you have to know in your mind that what I'm saying is would you care
关心一块巧克力，你必须在脑海中知道我所说的是你会关心
for a piece of chocolate.
一块巧克力。
I can't say like a piece of chocolate I can say.
我不能说像一块巧克力我可以说。
Would you like a piece of chocolate.
你想要一块巧克力吗？
Cannot say like a piece of chocolate.
不能说像一块巧克力。
Care for a piece of chocolate.
照顾一块巧克力。
Yes I can say that.
是的，我可以这么说。
That's very common means I would like to know if you would like that.
这是很常见的意思，我想知道你是否愿意。
But because it's spoken English we often cancel Would you just say care for very common now.
但是因为是英语口语，所以我们经常取消你会不会说现在很常见。
It could mean that I have a cup of coffee right here and I give it to you.
这可能意味着我在这里有一杯咖啡，我把它给你。
Probably not though.
可能不是。
What does it probably mean.
大概是什么意思。
It probably means I would like you to go with me to get some coffee together.
这可能意味着我希望你和我一起去喝杯咖啡。
So you'll stand up from your desk if we're maybe we're co-workers.
所以如果我们可能是同事，你会从你的办公桌上站起来。
Hey hey.
嘿嘿。
Care for a cup of coffee.
照顾一杯咖啡。
Yeah sure.
好，当然。
Stand up.
站起来。
Go.
去。
That's a way of saying.
这是一种说法。
Would you like to go with me to get a cup of coffee.
你愿意和我一起去喝杯咖啡吗？
Again it can be used if it's something that I have right here and I want to know if you want that thing
如果它是我在这里拥有的东西并且我想知道你是否想要那个东西，它可以再次使用
then I can also say care for a care for a whatever this is.
那么我也可以说关心一个关心这个是什么。
You can say Oh yeah sure.
你可以说哦，是的，当然。
Yeah sure.
好，当然。
Yeah.
是的。
Sure.
当然。
If you want to agree right away just say yeah great.
如果您想立即同意，请说是的，太好了。
Yes.
是的。
Sure sounds good.
当然听起来不错。
Sounds great sometimes of course it's like I can't believe you didn't ask me before.
有时听起来很棒，当然这就像我不敢相信你以前没有问过我一样。
Of course means absolutely yes.
当然意味着绝对是的。
In fact we can say absolutely.
事实上，我们可以说绝对。
Absolutely.
绝对地。
Absolutely means absolutely yes.
绝对意味着绝对是。
Very strong.
非常强壮。
Yes.
是的。
Right.
正确的。
Definitely.
确实。
We can say definitely as well.
我们也可以肯定地说。
There are lots of different ways to agree and say yes.
有很多不同的方式来同意和说是。
Sounds good.
听起来不错。
Yes sure.
是的，当然。
These are all very very common in this sort of situation and lots of other situations very common ways
这些在这种情况下都是非常常见的，在许多其他情况下也是非常常见的方式
to agree to things and say yes to questions.
同意事情并对问题说“是”。
Absolutely.
绝对地。
Yes of course.
是的当然。
Definitely.
确实。
Sure.
当然。